For too long, the leaders of this nation have given average Americans less than they deserve.
They refuse to fully express their support for those who need it most.
America needs someone who can say what they mean and mean what they say.
And say it, with their full chest, ten toes down.
Someone who sees all of America.
The good.
The bad.
And the raggedy.
America is quite the fixer-upper.
And it needs someone who is used to doing what the haters call too much.
Someone who can carry the workload of numerous web series, a singing career, a syndicated radio show, network television, and puppy potty training.
Someone who is built differently from the rest of American leadership.
And can give this country the Vicks vapor rub and ginger ale it needs to get on its feet.
There are many Americans who need support, honesty, and levity.
And Amanda is here to give you what you need.